// Geography
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The Sankosh river forms boundary between which of the following two states?",
    answer: "Assam and West Bengal",
    options: [
      "Bihar and West Bengal",
      "Assam and Arunachal Pradesh",
      "Assam and West Bengal",
      "Bihar and Jharkhand"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "With which of the following countries, India shares maximum length of border?",
    answer: "Bangladesh",
    options: [
      "Pakistan",
      "China",
      "Nepal",
      "Bangladesh"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following two rivers empty in Gulf of Khambhat?",
    answer: "Narmada and Tapti rivers",
    options: [
      "Narmada and Tapti rivers",
      "Jhelum and Tapti",
      "Jhelum and Ravi",
      "Tapti and Godavari"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which among the following South Indian states shared its boundary with the maximum number of other states?",
    answer: "Karnataka",
    options: [
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Karnataka",
      "Kerala",
      "Andhra Pradesh"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following place has never got the vertical rays of the Sun?",
    answer: "Srinagar",
    options: [
      "Srinagar",
      "Mumbai",
      "Chennai",
      "Thiruvananthapuram"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Where is the India's permanent research station Dakshin Gangotri?",
    answer: "Antarctica",
    options: [
      "Great Himalayas",
      "Indian Ocean",
      "Antarctica",
      "Arabian Sea"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which State is called the sugar bowl of India?",
    answer: "Uttar Pradesh",
    options: [
      "Bihar",
      "Andhra Pradesh",
      "Chhattisgarh",
      "Uttar Pradesh"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which is the highest dam in India?",
    answer: "Tehri dam",
    options: [
      "Hirakud dam",
      "Tehri dam",
      "Nagarjuna Sagar dam",
      "Bhakra dam"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the name of southernmost hill ranges in India?",
    answer: "Cardamom Hills",
    options: [
      "Nilgiri Hills",
      "Annamalai Hills",
      "Nallamalai Hills",
      "Cardamom Hills"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following coast where is Gulf of Mannar is located?",
    answer: "Tamil Nadu",
    options: [
      "Kerala",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Karnataka",
      "Andhra Pradesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following is a deadlock country located next to india ?",
    answer: "Nepal",
    options: [
      "China",
      "Pakistan",
      "Bangladesh",
      "Nepal"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Least populated country in the world?",
    answer: "Vatican City",
    options: [
      "Monaco",
      "Vatican City",
      "Nepal",
      "Madagascar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Richat Structure is located in which desert?",
    answer: "Sahara Desert",
    options: [
      "Thar Desert",
      "Gobi Desert",
      "Kalahari Desert",
      "Sahara Desert"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Smallest Dwarf planet in solar system",
    answer: "Hygiea",
    options: [
      "Pluto",
      "Ceres",
      "Hygiea",
      "Eris"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Sea seperating Europe and Africa is",
    answer: "Mediterranean Sea",
    options: [
      "Black Sea",
      "Red Sea",
      "Mediterranean Sea",
      "Caspian Sea"
    ]
  },
];